http://www.clearstream.com/clearstream-en/privacy-policy-1277786

Back to page
Print
Skip to
navigation (Press Enter).
Skip to main
content (Press Enter).
Company Governance
Shareholding StructureSupervisory BoardsExecutive ManagementBoard of DirectorsGender DiversityGroup CommitteesCBF CommitteesAudit Committee Remuneration CommitteeRisk CommitteeUser CommitteeCBL CommitteesAudit CommitteeNomination CommitteeRemuneration CommitteeRisk CommitteeUser CommitteeInternal Control Framework
Corporate Responsibility
Art collection
Due Diligence Information
AFMEAGC QuestionnaireBusiness Continuity ManagementComplianceCompliance Questionnaire and ISSA DDQWolfsberg questionnaireGDPRTechnical and organisational measures (Article 32)Notice of European Union Data Protection TermsISAE Report
Awards and Achievements
Regulation
BaFin Three Point DeclarationLicencesCPMI-IOSCO Disclosure FrameworkCentral Securities Depositories Regulation (CSDR)Customer ReadinessCSDR requirements for Transfer Agents and RegistrarsCode of conductPrice transparencyAccess & InteroperabilityUnbundlingCompensation FundPillar III Disclosure ReportRegulatory OversightRemuneration informationGovernanceUSA Patriot Act Certification
Career
Open positionsStudents - InternsContactGraduatesRecruitment eventsProfessionalsOur offices
50 years of Clearstream
Reports and ratings
Company Governance
Due Diligence Information
Regulation
Who we are
Becoming a Clearstream customer
Corporate Responsibility
Awards and Achievements
Career
Products and Services
OneClearstream
Migration timelineRollout documentation
TARGET2-Securities
Your opportunityT2S essentialsT2S Release informationT2S-related information
Asset services
Asset services overviewCorporate actionsCorporate actions ICSDCorporate actions CSD LegacyIncome processingIncome processing ICSDAutomatic FXIncome processing CSDMarkdown serviceProxy VotingReportingTax and certificationCommon Reporting StandardCustomer Tax GuideCustomer trainingFATCASelf-certificationTaxboxTax MatrixTax Reclaim ServiceUpload BO listFAQsNews
Cash and banking services
Cash and banking overviewEligible currenciesCommercial bank money servicesTreasuryAutomatic FXCreditIntraday Technical OverdraftUnconfirmed Funds FacilityOffshore RenminbiUmbrella credit and collateral servicesCentral bank money servicesT2S DCA cash reporting service
Connectivity
CASCADE/T2SCASCADE OnlineCASCADE via File TransferCASCADE via SWIFTCASCADE via MQT2S DCP ConnectivityCASCADE formsCash ReportsLending ReportsSettlement ReportsCustody ReportsInformation ReportsTaxbox formsJob Setup Request formsRelease informationTesting and SimulationAvailabilityClearstreamXactXact Web PortalXact File TransferClearstreamXact application formsXact via SWIFTRelease informationCreationOnlineSWIFT MyStandardsVestima
Global Securities Financing
Global Liquidity HubGlobal Liquidity Hub for OTC derivativesGlobal Liquidity Hub with T2SGlobal Liquidity Hub ICSD servicesTriparty collateral services (CmaX)RepoTriparty RepoGC Pooling€GCSecurities lendingCollateral managementPledge to central banksCCP marginingInitial margin segregationSecurities lending and borrowingAutomated Securities Lending and BorrowingASLASL principalStrategic securities lendingPrincipal lending (ASLplus)Agency lending via CCPSecurities lending for central banksSFTR Reporting Support ServiceGlobal Liquidity Hub CSD servicesTriparty collateral services (Xemac)Pledge to central banksCCP marginingServices for secured instrumentsGC PoolingSecurities lending and borrowingKAGplusGlobal Liquidity Hub partnershipsLiquidity Hub CollectLiquidity Hub ConnectLiquidity Hub GOLiquidity Hub SelectLiquidity AllianceMembersResearchNewslettersNewsKey documentationSLB ratesContactsBusiness development and Client relationsEurope, Middle East and AfricaUK, Ireland and AmericasAPACSecurities Lending DistributionProduct ManagementOperations
Investment Fund Services
VestimaDistributors and Fund PlatformsOrdering fundsSettlement and CustodySettlementCustodyTransfer servicesRegistrar Monitoring ReportInvestment Funds Reference DataFund AcceptanceTransparency of holdingsInvestment Funds as CollateralFund ProvidersReceiving ordersSettlement and CustodyISIN Issuance and AcceptanceCSDR requirements for Transfer Agents and RegistrarsTransparencyTransparency of holdingsTransparency of transactionsCentral Facility for FundsAML and KYCMarket coverageAustraliaBelgiumCayman IslandsCanadaChinaCyprusEstoniaFinlandFranceIndonesiaIrelandLiechtensteinMalaysiaNetherlandsNorwaySingaporeSouth AfricaSwedenSt Vincent and the GrenadinesThailandUnited States of AmericaFund CentreFund ProvidersDistribution PartnersFund SpotlightAustraliaCore custodyUnit price dataLook-through underlying investment dataDistribution dataTax component dataSpecialised fund data servicesElectronic PDS LibaryETFsNewsKey documentationContacts
Issuance
European Issuer PortalIssuance with T2SIssuance modelsICSDCSDIssuance servicesAdvisory servicesSecurities admissionCode allocationCode pre-allocationElectronic document transferPrimary DistributionPost-issuance servicesMarkups and markdownsDisclosureRegistered sharesSecured instrumentsSafekeeping and vaultsReference Data Services
IT Solutions
OverviewHosting solutionsOperational solutionsNewsContacts
Settlement
Commercial bank money settlement (ICSD)Settlement overviewInternalBridgeExternalThe settlement dayLocal market time deadlinesSettlement processing cyclesNetting algorithmsCentral bank money (CSD)Settlement typesSettlement cyclesStock Exchange and Eurex CCP tradesSettlement servicesTrading venues and CCP settlementTrading venuesCentral counterpartiesCC&GLCH SA RepoClearLCH Ltd EquityclearICSD pre-matching servicesICSD matching servicesICSD umbrella credit & collateralICSD automatic securities lending (ASL)ICSD settlement sequence managementICSD fails managementCSD CASCADE FOP matchingICSD and CSD CASCADE realignmentCSD GBC conversionsCSD TEFRA DCSD registered sharesRegistered shares announcementsRegistered Shares in CSCInvestors PortalFAQsNews
Market coverage
Markets coveredMulti-market securitiesAmericasArgentinaAnnouncementsCanadaAnnouncementsMexicoAnnouncements United States of AmericaAnnouncementsUruguayAnnouncements
Asia PacificAustraliaAnnouncements ChinaAnnouncementsHong KongAnnouncementsIndonesiaAnnouncementsJapanAnnouncements
MalaysiaAnnouncementsNew ZealandAnnouncementsPhilippinesAnnouncementsSingaporeAnnouncementsSouth KoreaAnnouncementsTaiwanAnnouncementsThailandAnnouncementsEurope T2SAustriaAnnouncementsBelgiumAnnouncementsDenmarkAnnouncementsEstoniaAnnouncementsFinlandAnnouncementsFranceAnnouncementsGermanyAnnouncementsGreeceAnnouncementsHungaryAnnouncementsItalyAnnouncementsLatviaAnnouncementsLithuaniaAnnouncementsLuxembourgAnnouncementsMaltaAnnouncementsNetherlandsAnnouncementsPortugalAnnouncementsRomaniaAnnouncementsSlovak RepublicAnnouncementsSloveniaAnnouncementsSpainAnnouncementsSwitzerlandAnnouncementsEurope non-T2SArmeniaAnnouncementsBulgariaAnnouncementsCroatiaAnnouncementsCyprusAnnouncementsCzech RepublicAnnouncementsGeorgiaAnnouncementsIcelandAnnouncementsIrelandAnnouncementsKazakhstanAnnouncementsNorwayAnnouncementsPolandAnnouncementsRussiaAnnouncementsSwedenAnnouncementsTurkeyAnnouncementsUkraineAnnouncementsUnited KingdomAnnouncementsMiddle East and AfricaDubai (Nasdaq Dubai)AnnouncementsIsraelAnnouncementsSouth AfricaAnnouncementsInternationalAnnouncementsBridge
Asset types
SecuritiesFixed Income SecuritiesEquitiesDepository receiptsInvestment Fund ServicesEntitlementsStructured productsCashOthers
OneClearstream
Asset services
Connectivity
Investment Fund Services
IT Solutions
Market coverage
TARGET2-Securities
Cash and banking services
Global Securities Financing
Issuance
Settlement
Asset types
Strategy and Initiatives
Asset safety
CSDR Article 38 disclosureVestima Asset SafetyInvestor Money Regulation (IMR)Clearstream Default Management
Market harmonisation
ISMAGISMAG OrganisationRecommendations and Market Practice BookTaxonomyAt issuanceDuring a security’s life cycle - post-issuancePublicationsMarket Framework
China strategy
China Bond LinkBond ConnectStock ConnectMutual Recognition of FundsCEINEXStudies
Regulatory solutions
AIFMD & UCITS VCapital Markets UnionEMIRSFTRSRD II
Partnerships
Liquidity AllianceMembersResearchTradecycle
Studies
Associated businessesEurex Clearing CCP white paperCollateral management practices of central banksETFs: Challenges of fragmentationFinding the best level of transparencyMutual Recognition for Funds - Mainland China/Hong KongOperational transition in wealth managementOur innovative solutions for the ETF marketRMB internationalisationThe Changing Dynamics of Investment Fund ProcessingT2S potential to reduce Basel III capital shortfallThe Future of Global Debt Issuance: 2025 Outlook The Global Financial and Monetary System in 2030The T2S OpportunityWhat's next for funds?
Bylined articles
Settlement and CustodyGlobal Securities FinancingInvestment Fund ServicesIndustry ThoughtsFinTech
Videos
Asset safety
China strategy
Partnerships
Bylined articles
Market harmonisation
Regulatory solutions
Studies
Privacy Policy
Under this privacy notice (hereinafter the “Notice”), Clearstream (hereinafter “We” or “Us”) informs you how We process your personal data. Your personal data means any information relating to you (hereinafter the “Personal Data”), such as name or contact details.We pay special attention on the processing of Personal Data in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation EU 2016/679 (“GDPR”) and applicable national data protection laws.Please find further information in the Notice of European Union Data Protection Terms.1. Controller1.1. Our identity and contact detailsWe are:Clearstream Banking S.A.42, avenue JF KennedyL-1855 LuxembourgLuxembourgPhone: +352-243-0Email: web@clearstream.com1.2. Contact details of data protection officerData Protection OfficerClearstream Banking S.A.42 Avenue JF KennedyL-1855 LuxembourgLuxembourgor send an email to: dataprotection@clearstream.comIf you have further questions regarding data protection and privacy of your personal data at Clearstream Banking AG please contact:Data Protection OfficerClearstream Banking AGMergenthalerallee 6165760 EschbornGermanyor send an email to: dataprotection@clearstream.comIf you have further questions regarding data protection and privacy of your personal data at Clearstream Banking S.A. Singapore Branch please contact:Data Protection OfficerClearstream Banking S.A. Singapore Branch9 Raffles Place#55-01 Republic PlazaSingapore 048619Republic of SingaporeTelephone: +65 65971623 2. Purpose, Categories of Personal Data, Legal Basis and Retention2.1. Categories of your Personal Data and purposes of Our processingWe process the following categories of your Personal Data for the following purposes:2.1.1. Name, address, telephone number or email address if you wish to make direct contact with us, register for a newsletter or a closed user group. Which data is collected in the various entry masks depends on the individual entry fields. Mandatory information fields will be marked accordingly. All other information shall be voluntary, and;2.1.2. web servers will only store the shortened address of your internet service provider (i.e. the shortened IP address), the name of the website from where you visit us, our websites that you retrieve, the used web browser type and the date and duration of your visit. Any relation to an individual person is not established due to the shortened IP address.2.2. Legal basis for Our processing of your Personal DataOur processing of your Personal Data is allowed by law. The legal basis is:2.2.1. As to the processing of your Personal Data under Section 2.1.1.: The legal basis for processing of Personal Data for personalised services is Art. 6 para. 1 lit. (b) of the GDPR permitting the processing of your Personal Data for the purposes of providing Our personalised services to you.2.3. Do you have to provide your Personal Data to Us?The provision of your Personal Data is necessary to access the protected areas of this website which is limited to members of Our customer groups, to make direct contact with us, or to receive a newsletter. This means that you are obliged to provide your Personal Data to Us as part of a user registration process when making use of these options. Such Personal Data remain under your control at all times via the “My Profile” facility. Your user account can be viewed or modified at any time by you, the account owner.The consequences if you do not provide your Personal Data to Us are that the respective service offered may no longer be available.2.4. Do We make automated decisions on you?We do not make any automated decisions solely on automatic processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects concerning you or similarly significantly affects you.2.5. Retention periodsThe period for which your Personal Data will be stored by Us is shown in the table below:Personal DataRetention PeriodName, address, telephone number or email addressAs long as necessary to carry out our relationship with you.Shortened IP addressThe shortened IP address will then be deleted without delay as soon as it is no longer required.3. Transfer of Personal Data to Third PartiesWe will not transfer your Personal Data to third parties except such transfer is permitted by law or you have explicitly consented to the transfer.We may transfer your Personal Data to public authorities where this is required by the applicable law. A transfer of your Personal Data is also permitted if there is a suspicion of a criminal offence or the abuse of the services offered on our website. In this event, We shall be entitled to transfer your Personal Data to the criminal prosecution authority.Otherwise, your personal data will be stored exclusively in our database and on our servers, or on those of our commissioned data processing providers. We will only share your Personal Data with other controllers for their own purposes such as cooperation or advertising partners under the condition that you explicitly and voluntarily agreed to such transfer of your Personal Data; in this case, we will obtain your consent separately from this Notice.4. CookiesWhen you visit the website and Our online platform, information is stored on your terminal device in the form of a "cookie." Cookies are small files that are stored on your terminal device and save certain settings and data to exchange with our websites via your browser.For example, cookies enable us to tailor a website to better match your interests or to store your password so that you do not have to re-enter it every time. As a general rule, we never collect personal data via cookies, unless you have given us your express permission to do so.If you do not want us to recognize your terminal device, please configure your Internet browser to erase all cookies from your device, to block all cookies or to receive a warning before a cookie is stored. You will find brief instructions on how to do this below.Please note that certain functions of our website may no longer work, or not correctly, without cookies.a. Types of cookiesCookies can be assigned to four categories, depending on their function and intended purpose: absolutely necessary cookies, performance cookies, functional cookies, and cookies for marketing purposes.i. Absolutely necessary cookiesAre needed for you to navigate within websites and operate basic website functions, such as the issuance of anonymous Session IDs for bundling several related queries to a server.ii. Performance cookiescollect information on the usage of our websites, including for example the Internet browsers and operating systems used, the domain name of the website which you previously visited, the number of visits, average duration of visit, and pages called up. These cookies do not store any information that would make it possible to personally identify the user. The information collected with the aid of these cookies is aggregated and is therefore anonymous. Performance cookies serve the purpose of improving the user friendliness of a website and therefore enhancing the user’s experience. You can block the use of such cookies by creating an exclusion cookie (see “managing cookies” below).iii. Functional cookiesenable a website to store information the user has already entered (such as user ID, language selection, or the user’s location), in order to offer improved, personalized functions to the user. Functional cookies are also used to enable requested functions such as playing videos and to make a user’s decision to block or disable a certain function (e.g. web analysis) - “opt-out cookies”.iv. Cookies for marketing purposesare used to offer more relevant content to users, based on their specific interests. They are also used to limit the display frequency of an ad and to measure and control the effectiveness of advertising campaigns. They register whether users have visited a website or not, and which contents were used. This information may possibly also be shared with third parties, such as advertisers, for example. These cookies are often linked to the functions of third-party websites. You can block the use of such cookies by creating an opt-out cookie (see “Managing cookies” below).b. Cookies on Our website and Our online platform
Please note: Not all of the cookies mentioned above will necessarily be used when you browse our website using a mobile terminal device.c. Managing cookiesYou can change your cookie preferences at any time by clicking on the ‘Cookies Preference Manager’ link. You can then adjust the available sliders to ‘On’ or ‘Off’, then clicking ‘Save and close’. You may need to refresh your page for your settings to take effect.d. How can I deactivate cookies?In the following you will find a summary of links that provide detailed information on the deactivation of cookies in commonly used browsers.Mozilla Firefox (https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored)Internet Explorer (https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies)Google Chrome (https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416?hl=en)Safari (https://support.apple.com/en-en/guide/safari/sfri11471/mac)5. Google AnalyticsOn the basis of our interest in the analysis and optimisation of our online offer within the meaning of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f. GDPR We use Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google LLC ("Google"). Google uses cookies. The information generated by the cookie about the use of the online offer by users is in general transferred to a Google server in the USA and stored there.Google will use the information on our behalf to for example evaluate the use of our online offer by users and to compile reports on the activities within this online offer. Pseudonymous user profiles can be created from the processed data.We use Google Analytics only with IP anonymisation enabled. This means that Google will shorten the IP address of users within Member States of the European Union or in other states party to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be transmitted to a Google server in the USA and shortened there.The IP address transmitted by the user's browser is not merged with other Google data. Users can prevent the storage of cookies by setting their browser software accordingly; users can also prevent Google from collecting the data generated by the cookie and relating to their use of the online offer and the processing of this data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under the following link: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.Further information on data use by Google, possible settings and objections can be found in Google's data protection declaration (https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads) and in the settings for the display of advertisements by Google (https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated).Users' personal data will be deleted or made anonymous after 14 months.6. Webtrends AnalyticsThis website uses Webtrends Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Webtrends EMEA Acquisition Ltd. / Webtrends Inc. ("Webtrends"). Webtrends uses cookies that are stored on your computer to collect anonymous data on how our website is being used. The information We collect helps us to adapt our website to the needs of our visitors.Webtrends stores information about the pages you visit on our website, how long you spend on each page, how you got to the site, and how many times you have accessed our site.Webtrends deletes client data, including backups, within ninety (90) days following termination of the agreement. Webtrends leverages data collection centers in Australia, Netherlands, and the United States. All data is processed and stored in the United States.You can opt out of receiving cookies from Webtrends by following the instructions at: https://ondemand.webtrends.com/support/optout.asp.For more information, please refer to the Webtrends Privacy Statement: https://www.webtrends.com/terms-policies/privacy/privacy-statement/.7. Your RightsUnder applicable data protection laws, you have rightsof access to, rectification of, and/or erasure of your Personal Data;to restrict or object to its processing;to tell Us that you do not wish to receive marketing information; and(in some circumstances) to require certain of your Personal Data to be transferred to you or a third party, which you can exercise by contacting Us at the details set out at the beginning of this Notice.To the extent our processing of your Personal Data is based on your consent, you also have the right to withdraw your consent, without affecting the lawfulness of our processing based on your consent before its withdrawal.To exercise your rights, you can contact Us as set out in Section 1.1above. You can also lodge a complaint about our processing of your Personal Data with a data protection authority.8. Data SecurityClearstream and our web operator, ]init[ AG für digitale Kommunikation Köpenicker Str. 9 10997 Berlin, use appropriate technical and organisational security measures in order to protect the data We have under our control against accidental or intentional manipulation, loss, destruction as well as access by unauthorised persons. Our security procedures are continually enhanced as new technology becomes available.Further privacy noticesClearstream Baking S.A. (CBL)Clearstream Banking AG (CBF)Customers and suppliersPrivacy Notice to Customers and SuppliersDatenschutzhinweis für Kunden und ZuliefererPrivacy Notice to Customers and SuppliersDatenschutzhinweis für Kunden und ZuliefererEventsPrivacy Notice for EventsDatenschutzhinweis für VeranstaltungenPrivacy Notice for EventsDatenschutzhinweis für Veranstaltungen
© Clearstream
Imprint
Disclaimer
Privacy Policy
Trademarks
Complaints
Top
Related Sites
